<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Solutions on Wealth Innovations Inc.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/solutions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Solutions on Wealth Innovations Inc.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021-2024 Wealth Innovations Inc. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Start-up</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/solutions/start-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/solutions/start-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;congratulations-on-beginning-your-new-career&#34;&gt;Congratulations on beginning your new career.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You have already invested tremendous time and effort to position yourself for a fulfilling and successful career. With this exciting opportunity, however, comes great responsibility, long hours and both personal and business risk. That’s why it is so important to plan early and prepare accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;consider-the-following&#34;&gt;Consider the following:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Have you contemplated what the impact of an unexpected illness or serious disability would have on you and your family’s financial security? Your single greatest asset is your ability to earn an income. For example, if you earn $100,000 a year for thirty years, indexed at 5% annually, your total lifetime earnings would be $6,976,078.99 Protecting your earning power through disability and critical illness insurance is imperative.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Career</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/solutions/mid-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/solutions/mid-career/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You have gained significant experience and built a successful business or professional practice. You have developed many meaningful relationships both personally and professionally. At this stage of life, accumulating and protecting wealth is an important priority.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other top financial priorities, aside from maintaining the lifestyle you have become accustomed to, most likely include planning for your children&amp;rsquo;s education and your eventual retirement. Some questions you may also want to ask yourself include:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/solutions/retirement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/solutions/retirement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;as-you-enter-the-twilight-of-your-career-or-perhaps-you-have-already-reached-retirement-you-reflect-on-how-time-has-passed-so-quickly&#34;&gt;As you enter the twilight of your career, or perhaps you have already reached retirement, you reflect on how time has passed so quickly.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems like only yesterday you began what has turned out to be a very successful career. With a degree of trepidation, you realize that you will now be drawing on your assets for the rest of your life; quite an adjustment after decades of accumulating wealth- you no longer have a paycheck.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exit Strategies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/solutions/exit_strategies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/solutions/exit_strategies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;if-you-own-a-business-or-have-a-professional-practice-a-significant-part-of-your-planning-will-include-preparing-for-the-eventual-transfer-or-sale-of-the-business&#34;&gt;If you own a business or have a professional practice, a significant part of your planning will include preparing for the eventual transfer or sale of the business.&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Planning in advance for this eventuality is imperative. You need to identify the team of professionals that you will work with through this process. It is also very important that these trusted team members coordinate their efforts to ensure that you get the very best outcome. Some of the issues that need to be considered during this process include:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRSP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/solutions/rrsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/solutions/rrsp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;REGISTERED RETIREMENT SAVINGS PLANS (RRSPS)&#xA;Are you looking to reduce your tax liability this year?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are you wondering how to approach Registered Retirement Savings Plans (RRSPs) in time to file your&#xA;taxes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every year the CRA allows you to contribute to your RRSP 60 days past the end of the year and still have&#xA;it count towards your RRSP contribution for the previous tax year.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year you have until March 1st, 2023.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
